grantnow.com 2008-04-08

# Grant Now

**Privacy Policy** \- Last Revised March 20, 2008 

By visiting this web site you are accepting the practices described in Strategic Financial Publishing, incorporated’s Privacy Policy.

GrantNow.com is owned and operated by Strategic Financial Publishing, Inc. and created this Privacy Policy with respect to information gathered on Web Pages hosted by GrantNow.com. Please be aware that we appreciate the trust you place in us by providing information on this web site, and our commitment to you is to use this information with both care and sensitivity. The information we collect from visitors to our web site helps us continually improve the products we offer to our valued customers. Types of information collected are outlined as follows:

  * Any information you voluntarily enter on our web site is maintained by Strategic Financial Publishing, Inc. to help us improve both the web site and product(s) advertised on the web site.  

  * In addition, we use “cookies” (as do the vast majority of other companies that do business on the World Wide Web) when you visit our site, which are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser. Information we collect and analyze via cookies includes the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system and platform, date and time of your visit, and cookie number. If you do not wish to have cookies placed on your computer, please review the options listed in the Help portion of the toolbar on your computer. The toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.

**Strategic Financial Publishing, Inc. periodically sends e-mail offers to its web site visitors on behalf of other businesses.** By providing information on this web site, you are agreeing to receive these periodic e-mail offers, which Strategic Financial Publishing, Inc. believes may be of interest to you as a consumer. If you do not wish to receive e-mail offers from us, please be sure to scroll down to the bottom of the first e-mail you receive and click on the opt-out link provided, which will remove your e-mail address from our database. You will then receive no further e-mail communications from us. If you do not scroll down to the bottom of the first e-mail you receive (or any e-mails thereafter), you will continue to receive e-mail offers from Strategic Financial Publishing, Inc. until you choose to click on the opt-out link that will be provided in each e-mail you receive from us. Or you can go to our opt-out form at [http://www.ebookidea.com](http://www.ebookidea.com/).

When you register with GrantNow.com and you select “Yes, I want to receive information and special offers from EntrepreneurialOptions.com” – you explicitly authorize to share your information with Datran Media to contact you via email.

We will, however, release account and other personal information when such release is necessary to comply with any state, federal or international laws, or when, in our judgment, we determine it to be necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of Strategic Financial Publishing, Inc. or our valued customers. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

Please note that Strategic Financial Publishing, Inc.’s web site uses secure payment processing company, Litle , who encrypts all financial information you input when you place an order. Any and all financial transactions you make through Strategic Financial Publishing, Inc.’s payment systems will be protected while you are doing business on our web site.

If you have any concern about privacy at Strategic Financial Publishing, Inc.’s web site, please [contact us](http://businessedgenetwork.com/cs.php) and we will make every effort to address your inquiry in a timely manner. 

Strategic Financial Publishing Inc. reserves the right to add to, delete from or in any other way modify any or all of this Privacy Policy without prior notification.

Close Window
